So, here's another thing that we could do with this list of rainbow colors.
这是另一个我们可以用彩虹色的列表做的事情
This turtle draws six different colored stars and here's how it does it.
这只乌龟有六种不同颜色的星星
From the top, we start out by defining a turtle and setting the turtles width to five,
从顶部开始 我们开始定义海龟 将海龟的宽度设置为 5 个
so they'll be nice and vivid.
这样他们就会变得善良生动
I'm setting the speed to zero which is the fastest just so it will draw very quickly.
我将速度设置为零 这是最快的速度 因此速度非常快
Then we have the loop for color in rainbow.
然后我们有了彩虹色的循环
So, this color variable is going to get each one of
所以这个颜色变量会让每个人
these values coming from the list each time we go through this loop,
每次我们通过这个循环时 这些值都来自列表
red, then orange, then yellow, and so on.
红色 然后是橙色 然后是黄色等等
The first thing we do inside the loop is set the color of the turtle and then,
我们在回路里做的第一件事就是设置乌龟的颜色然后
we have a nested loop for side in 1, 2, 3,
我们有一个嵌套循环用于 1  2   3
4, 5, while this is just drawing a single star.
4   5  而这只是画了一颗星星
Then after drawing one star,
在画了一颗星星之后
the rest of the loop moves off to the position for the next star.
剩下的线圈就会移动到下一星的位置
Turns right by 60, picks the pen up,
右转 60 把笔捡起来
scoots over by 50 pixels to go from one star over to the place for the next star,
50 个像素从一个星星到下一星的位置
and puts the pen down.
把笔放下
Then, when we go to the top of the loop,
然后 当我们走到环的顶端时
we get a new color and draw a new star.
我们会有一种新的颜色画出一个新的星星